[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Gypsophila flowers are sometimes referred to as this.", "correct_answer": "Babys breath", "incorrect_answers": ["Arum", "Lady Banks", "Gypsy rose"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What lobe in the brain is responsible for retaining verbal memory?", "correct_answer": "Left Temporal Lobe", "incorrect_answers": ["Left Parietal Lobe", "Right Temporal Lobe", "Right Parietal Lobe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character did Bruce Willis voice in the 2003 animated movie Rugrats Go Wild?", "correct_answer": "Spike", "incorrect_answers": ["Toa", "Siri", "Dr. Lipshitz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which season did ancient Greeks celebrate Mothers Day?", "correct_answer": "Spring", "incorrect_answers": ["Winter", "Summer", "Fall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The actors playing Clarice Starling and Hannibal Lecter won the Best Actor and Best Actress Academy Awards.", "correct_answer": "The Silence of the Lambs", "incorrect_answers": ["Platoon", "Gladiator", "American Beauty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were the first names of the Blues Brothers in the 1980 movie by the same name?", "correct_answer": "Elwood and Jake", "incorrect_answers": ["Dagwood and Johnnie", "Woody and Oscar", "Dan and John"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To what geographical area is the Ctenomorphodes chronus, a species of stick insect, endemic?", "correct_answer": "Australia", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Madagascar", "South America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Hollywood actress starred in Steven Spielbergs 1982 movie E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial as little Gertie?", "correct_answer": "Drew Barrymore", "incorrect_answers": ["Julia Roberts", "Cameron Diaz", "Pamela Anderson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the role of Rebecca Howe on the TV show Cheers?", "correct_answer": "Kirstie Alley", "incorrect_answers": ["Rhea Perlman", "Shelley Long", "Bebe Neuwirth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a synonym for neutron star.", "correct_answer": "Pulsar", "incorrect_answers": ["White  Dwarf", "Black hole", "Questars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Harrison Ford did his own stunts for Indiana Jones and the Crystal Skull.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Siemens models has a built-in camera?", "correct_answer": "SF65", "incorrect_answers": ["M56", "S56", "CF62"]}]